You're a night agent now.
Relationships are dangerous.
I suggest no longer having
any personal contacts.
You're here because
POTUS pushed you on us.
not because you cleared the usual hurdles.
- Nobody can know where I am right now.
- Lock the family in the fridge.
Prepare the chemist
and his assistant for the lab.
The secretary general
of the United Nations
has something I seek.
Bring me that file.
and I'll give you the location
of where Miss Larkin
is currently being held.
- Why send me?
- I can never resist a two-for-one deal.
High-security intel
and a inside man at Night Action?
Your secret's safe with me.
on one condition.
When I call. you answer.
Where is she?
Show us your hands!
As long as I'm a night agent.
people will try to use you.
I'm just tired of running.
and I just want a normal life.
Promise me something.
You're not gonna wait for me to call.
If you hear I'm in trouble.
you won't come look for me.
You forget about me.
You admitted to breaking
and entering into the United Nations.
stealing sensitive information
from the secretary general.
and to transferring said information to--
- What was the term you used?
- An intelligence broker.
Let's not forget who works for whom.
Governor Hagan's
virtually guaranteed the presidency now.
You aided and abetted in the swinging
of a presidential election.
This Broker is about to control
a sitting president.
The new mission. determine
the exact nature of their relationship.
The Broker still believes he owns you.
- What happens now?
- You wait for him to call.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hello?
Uh. Dr. Shepard. how are you?
No. I'm alone. Why?
Sorry?
No. uh… No. one second.
I don't understand. Um…
Spread where?
But how is that possible?
Dr. Reynolds said--
How many more rounds of treatment
are we talking about?
What are the other options?
Please. there has to be something.
How long?
Uh. sorry. just one second.
Um. everything okay. Peter?
Mom just needs a minute. okay?
I'll be right there.
- What are you looking for?
- The Lego man lost his pants.
Oh. Hmm.
Why are you sad?
Oh. it's nothing.
Mom's just being a little silly.
All right. come here.
Let's find those pants.
Oh!
You found it.
Now he can go on his next adventure.
Thanks.
How'd your dad and I get so lucky. huh?
Will you promise me something?
What?
Promise you'll always do the right thing…
even when it's hard.
Promise?
I promise.
Turn around.
You're late.
Your directions sucked.
We safe here?
We'll be fine.
Come on.
- Victor.
- Sandrine.
- Good to see you.
- Here. take a seat.
Actually. this will be brief.
We the highest bidder?
You are.
assuming all the cash you promised
is in that backpack.
Your turn.
Congratulations.
We almost went with the other bidder.
Anybody I'd know?
Sorry. you can't fault me for trying
to scope out the competition. right?
The password's 739824.
Schematics and blueprints
for the new Columbia-class nuclear sub
rolling into production next month.
Great. So we got a deal. then?
The. uh. first of many. hopefully.
I'll be in touch.
You guys mind if I ask you something?
Just out of curiosity?
It seems like you have a nice life.
good job. strong marriage. kids.
Why risk all that
to sell this to me and my client?
You probably wouldn't get it.
Try me.
Uh. our line of work.
our jobs at the Pentagon…
we sacrificed everything
for our country for years.
But all the secrecy. the pressure.
it took its toll on our family.
It took a lot.
Then. one day.
we decided to take some back.
Thanks.
Move in.
Some minor turbulence. folks.
Please stay seated
and keep your seatbelts on.
Next time I insist I'll be fine
on a ten-hour flight without an Ativan.
please remind me of this moment.
Hey… five hours left.
then we'll be home. we can sleep in.
Mom's even offered to come over
and cook us dinner.
Lovely evening with your mother.
Maybe I'll stay on the plane.
I'm joking. She's lovely…
to you.
What?
Uh. no. never mind.
It's probably nothing.
Hey. come here.
Cheese.
Peter.
- Deputy Director.
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- It's fine.
- DNI wanted an all-hands meeting.
- Pima 12?
- Lot of Americans went down on that plane.
President Hagan wants answers
and a target to go after.
Let's walk.
I have to pick up a necklace
I bought for my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
- I didn't know you. uh--
- High school sweethearts.
Reconnected on Facebook
after our divorces.
Still new.
Where's Catherine?
Cairo. Setting up a new agent.
Another one?
POTUS initiated five Night Actions
last month alone.
I'm training his new recruits
as fast as possible to meet demand.
How long's he planning
on keeping this pace up?
Doesn't show any signs of slowing down.
Says he wants to ensure his intelligence
agencies aren't compromised.
That's ironic.
considering The Broker
might be compromising him.
Might be. We still don't know
what we don't know.
So Michael. Sandrine.
what did we get from them?
They owned up to all of it.
It was a clean case. Good work.
How about their kids?
Where are they at now?
I believe there's an aunt.
I'll confirm.
What about the other bidder?
They give you a name? Is it The Broker?
Chinese national.
Ties to one of Beijing's
biggest defense contractors.
It's not the outcome you were hoping for.
- Yeah.
- I know.
You headed back to New York?
Depends.
When's the next mission?
We closed four cases in six months.
When was the last time
you went home. Peter?
It's been a while.
And Rose Larkin?
You two still in touch?
Why?
No.
But…
It's. uh. safer for her.
- The best agents know they need balance.
- What I need is for him to call.
The more important
The Broker thinks I am to Night Action.
the more likely he is
to reach out and make contact.
It's been almost a year.
This Broker may never call.
He has to.
You can't keep doing this
to yourself. Peter.
You stopped a terrorist attack at the UN.
You saved countless lives.
Yeah. but to do that. I had to let him go.
Okay? And now every time
there's a political assassination.
there's an intelligence leak.
terrorists shoot a plane out of the sky.
I gotta wonder if I'm responsible.
No. you aren't.
So why does it feel like I am?
Maybe you should take some time.
talk to someone about that.
Look. it sounds like you and Catherine
need as many agents as you can spare.
Yeah.
So where do you need me?
Two nights ago. Capitol Police
and then FBI responded to a gunshot
at a D.C. apartment
belonging to a Jay Batra.
a 28-year-old junior analyst at FinCEN.
FBI found reason to believe Batra
stole classified FinCEN intelligence.
But not before killing his supervisor.
Benjamin Wallace.
We're not sure yet
how important the intel he took is.
but we'd like to find out.
Before we even knew to look for him.
Jay Batra had fled the country.
POTUS initiated
the Night Action this morning.
Where is he now?
Hey. uh… merhaba.
You remember me?
Your boss. he. uh… he texted me.
The… the owner. he texted me to come here.
Uh…
FOUND THE FLOATING PIMA 12
Hey. uh. excuse me.
What is she saying?
All dead.
Jenny and me. our hearts break
for the families of all who were lost.
but especially the 157 Americans
on Flight Pima 12.
And to Raúl Zapata
and his animals in the LFS
who committed
this disgusting act of terror.
we will not allow the loss of innocent
American lives to go unanswered.
- My friend.
- Hey. merhaba.
Uh. you… you saw him?
He saw.
You saw… you saw this guy?
- Evet. Yes.
- When? Today?
- Just five minutes before.
- You saw this guy five minutes ago?
Did he say something?
What did… what did he do?
He bought a pide.
just like the last couple of times.
What was he. uh… what was he wearing?
Uh. a gray…
Like a sweatshirt. And a hat. Red.
Okay. did he… did he say anything?
Station?
Hey. you speak Turkish now.
Yeah. Uh. which station?
Sirkeci.
Sirkeci. He told him
to go through Spice Bazaar.
Thank you. Sağ ol.
Commission.
SPICE BAZAAR
Pardon.
- You buy or no?
- No. No. go for it.
You too. Yeah. Sorry.
Sorry.
Shit.
Quick update. Call me back when you can.
- Thank you. Can I take it to the room?
- Of course.
Uh. just a pilsner.
What do you think he's singing about?
Well. if I had to guess.
there was a woman
who met a man on the road.
and they traveled together.
and they fell in love.
But the relationship was doomed because
they were headed in different directions.
At least. I think that's what he said
before he started singing.
What direction are you headed in tonight?
Come on. that was pretty smooth. right?
Not the worst line I've heard.
but far from the best though.
What was the best?
You want to end up like him? Heartbroken?
Sounds like they were wasting
each other's time. no?
No. I…
I don't think so.
"Better to have loved and lost."
is that it?
Yeah. something like that.
Hmm.
That's experience talking.
Your fault or hers?
It was mine.
Yeah. it was definitely mine.
actually. Uh…
- My job got in the way.
- Maybe get a new one.
Believe me. um.
I've considered it. but I started a…
a new project last year.
And. uh. I just. I… I don't know.
I kind of wanna see it through to the end.
Is that what brings you to Istanbul. work?
- You?
- Same.
What do you do for a living?
Oh. nothing exciting.
Oh. that's too bad.
Just means we'll have to find something
exciting to do outside business hours.
Are you trying
to get your heart broken again?
Depends.
On?
Who's doing the breaking.
Ordinarily. when a handsome guy
makes me laugh and asks me out.
I'm inclined to say yes.
That's a great impulse.
You know. you should follow it.
Yes. But unfortunately.
I have plans tonight.
and I fly out tomorrow.
My loss.
I've seen you before.
I don't think so. I'd… I'd. uh…
- I think I'd remember.
- I have. somewhere.
Around the hotel. maybe.
Yeah. Yeah. maybe.
Probably.
It was nice meeting you.
Kevin.
Isabel.
Good to meet you.
- Have a nice trip. Kevin.
- You too. Safe travels.
Can I just get one more of these. please?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Bravo!
- Hello?
- You try that baklava place yet?
- I'm kind of busy. Catherine.
- Have them deliver. Thank me later.
Hey. Hey!
Be careful.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean. I'm trying to.
Not you. June.
I'm watching her for the afternoon.
My sister got a new job.
so I'm trying to help out more.
Tell her I said hey.
Uncle Peter says hi.
Hey. Uncle Peter.
I spoke with FinCEN earlier.
- Anything?
- Not really.
By all accounts.
Jay Batra was a great analyst.
Smart. straight arrow.
Never bumped heads with anyone.
let alone shoot a superior.
- What about his boss?
- Ben Wallace.
Stellar career at FinCEN.
Helped bring down some big fish.
But nothing out of the ordinary.
Something's off.
Batra never had
so much as a speeding ticket.
Then what? He kills Wallace and takes off
with classified intelligence?
Just doesn't add up.
- If you'd have seen him today…
- Wait. you saw him?
For a second. yeah. and then he. um…
got away from me.
- Well. how'd he look?
- Paranoid. exhausted.
Like he's barely keeping
his head above water.
Any idea what he's up to in Istanbul?
He made. uh. contact with this reporter.
Isabel De Leon.
- She writes for The Financial Register.
- A reporter?
- Strange.
- Yeah. that's what I'm saying. It just…
Just doesn't sound like somebody
trying to sell classified intelligence.
- Sounds like someone with a story to tell.
- Still. he killed someone.
So you're to treat him as armed and deadly
until confirmed otherwise.
- You got it?
- Yes. ma'am.
- Anything else?
- Hey. I gotta go. okay?
Okay. You keep me updated. And. Peter.
you be careful too. seriously.
Yeah. I'm… I'm trying to.
BEŞİKTAŞ JK - GÖZTEPE
ROW: G - SEAT: 34
He's inside.
We need tickets.
Excuse me.
Uh. sorry. that seat is taken.
Yeah. it's okay. We won't be here long.
- Hey. hey.
- Listen. Listen.
There are people looking for you. Okay?
They're here in the stadium.
It's in your best interest
to listen to me. You understand?
What do you want?
Open the backpack.
The FinCEN intelligence.
did you give it to that reporter?
How long have you been following me?
Answer the question.
Just a copy.
I left the originals back at my place.
Okay. here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna get you out of here. unharmed.
We're gonna go to the place
you've been holed up in.
You're gonna give me the intelligence.
All of that happens with no issues.
I'll give you five minutes to explain
to me why your boss's dead body
was found on your living room floor.
Deal?
- Shit.
- What?
Those guys have been following you
since the station yesterday.
- Wait. you were at the train station?
- Now stand up.
Do exactly what I tell you to do.
and we'll get out of here safely.
Now give me your phone.
Hat low. eyes low. stay close.
Let's go.
He isn't here.
He left the phone behind.
Yeah. I think he's telling the truth.
I'm looking at them now.
They're incomplete.
but there's definitely something here.
I need to call you back.
Run. Jay! Go!
Help!
Help! He stole my wallet!
Police!
Help!
He's headed for the main exit.
No!
Jay!
I'm trying to help you.
Help--
You run. I shoot. You scream. I shoot.
Okay?
I have him. Meet at the car.
Get in.
Hey. don't touch that.
Hey. Jay. we gotta go.
Actually. stay in the car.
Go!
Buckle up.
No shit!
- Who are those guys?
- I was hoping you could tell me.
Who are you?
Get down!
Where'd they go?
Oh shit!
We're gonna crash! We're gonna crash!
Check the glove box.
Any weapons?
- Uh. nothing.
- What about the back?
Toys and shit. Wait. there's something.
- Please tell me it's a gun.
- First aid kit.
- What's inside?
- Uh. bandages. gauze. rubbing alcohol.
Here. pour the alcohol into this.
Dude. you're making me spill.
- Now what?
- Stuff the gauze inside.
- Am I making a Molotov cocktail?
- Not quick enough.
Okay.
Light it.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Now!
I'm Peter.
Jay.
Yeah. I know.
Stay in the car.
Go ahead.
Night Action.
Code. please.
Leaf. tower. ice. blade.
- Copperhead?
- I'm on the western edge of Istanbul.
I need an extraction back stateside
for two people. ASAP.
Please hold.
It's just your adrenaline. Jay.
It'll pass.
- Is this normal for you?
- Stay close.
Soonest I can get you out
is tomorrow morning.
Tomorrow. no. I said I need it ASAP.
Please. There's gotta be something
you can do.
Our assets are spread thin.
We've only got one contractor
in the area currently.
and they're helping another agent.
I'm sorry.
This is the best I can do right now.
I booked a place for us.
About a half-mile up from here.
- You sure they won't find us?
- As long as you don't have your phone.
How'd they figure out my number?
I was using a burner. I was careful.
Did you call anybody while you were here?
My cousin. once.
She lives in the city. She helped me
find a place to crash before I got in.
That was probably it. Let's go.
Wait. you don't think
they're monitoring her phone. right?
I gotta warn her.
- I can't let you do that. Jay.
- No. she has kids.
I'll have somebody from my organization
give her a call from an untraceable line.
Your organization? What are you. FBI? CIA?
Postal inspector?
We're the people they call when agencies
like FinCEN need to be investigated.
I'm trying to figure out what happened
between you and your supervisor.
Now wait.
About a month ago.
our office received a bunch
of suspicious activity reports. SARs.
Transfers flagged by banks.
transactions between accounts
they think might be fraudulent.
What was in the reports?
Multiple large money transfers
from several American companies
to a crypto wallet. It was strange.
I told Wallace
we should investigate further.
He told me to drop it.
- He say why?
- Didn't have to.
Treasury receives
about four million SARs a year.
You gotta pick your battles.
and he's the one that gets to pick.
So five days ago. what happened?
He calls me. says he wants
to go over the SARS again.
then he comes over
and starts grilling me like.
did I tell anyone about them?
Did I keep digging
after he told me to stop?
Then he destroys the hard drive
with the SARs on it.
so I try to stop him. and he pulls a gun.
Says he's sorry that they made him do it.
"They"?
It made no sense.
I tried to talk him down.
get close enough to grab the gun. It just…
It went off.
Okay.
So why didn't you tell
anybody else at FinCEN?
Why not call the FBI? Why'd you run?
'Cause Wallace recruited me
to Treasury four years ago.
I've been to his house.
I've had dinner with his wife and kids.
I would've trusted him with my life
until he pulled that gun on me.
I was scared. I couldn't think straight.
didn't know who else was coming after me.
- Maybe it was stupid. but--
- It wasn't stupid.
Whoever's involved in these SARs.
they're just gonna keep coming.
So let's find what's left
of the originals. then maybe…
What?
I lied back at the stadium.
I don't actually have the originals.
Whatever copies I did have.
I gave to Isabel.
- I mean. I had photos on my phone. but…
- Yeah.
I thought going public with the documents
would make me safer.
So I sent tips out
to multiple journalists.
and Isabel's the only one who followed up.
She's even trying to get me asylum
at some consulate here.
What are you offering?
How about not dragging your ass back home
to a federal supermax?
Okay. great.
Listen. when we get back to the U.S..
we'll try to find the missing SARs.
If there's something in there.
we'll help figure it out.
You and your organization that can't even
get us out of here before tomorrow?
I think I'm better off taking my chances
with the Vietnamese or Cambodians.
Too bad I'm not giving you that option.
Now come on. let's go.
The. uh…
the extraction point's two miles away.
Okay?
Settle in.
Try to stay away from the windows.
I'm gonna make a call.
So on top of killing a federal agent.
you have him confessing
to leaking intelligence to the press.
He's scared. Catherine.
He's desperate. He made a mistake. Okay?
But you don't have to take my word for it.
Just debrief him when we land.
Hear it for yourself.
Assuming Mosley agrees.
and I buy what Jay is selling.
we could reach out to the journalist.
see if she hands the SARs over.
Or maybe the bank
that filed them has copies.
But if we can't find anything
that corroborates his story.
we're handing him over.
Understood?
Yeah. understood.
Who was that you were calling earlier?
I thought you were asleep. man.
I haven't slept since I ran.
That was my boss.
And?
She said she'd hear you out.
That we'll try to help you
find the missing SARs…
and give you a chance
to prove your innocence.
And if I can't?
I keep seeing him.
Wallace.
I didn't mean to…
kill him.
Look at me.
If it happened the way you said it did.
then it was self-defense.
It means he was covering something up.
okay?
Still. how can I know
I did the right thing?
You can't.
Not always. at least.
What if it's not just Wallace?
What if it's others?
What if it's all of FinCEN?
How do I prove I'm innocent
if the whole institution's rotten?
Jay. even if that's the case.
we'll figure it out. Okay?
I promise.
Believe it or not. uh.
I've been where you are.
You fled the country
with confidential Treasury documents
after killing your boss?
Not exactly where you are…
but same zip code.
How'd you get through it?
I…
had a partner.
Somebody that believed me.
That believed in me.
Sometimes that's enough.
You believe me?
How the hell did they find us?
Oh shit.
Did you call your cousin?
To warn her.
I was on the phone for 30 seconds.
Didn't think they could track it
that quickly.
This way!
Here. go!
Down the steps.
Hey. try and find an exit. okay?
- Wait. what about you?
- Go. now. I'll be fine.
Spread out.
What was that?
Pasha?
- What?
- Behind…
Hey. Jay. Hey. you good?
Look at me. Look at me.
Hey. you good?
- Did you find an exit?
- Yeah.
- Show me.
- Let's go.
Come on. let's go.
Hey. Jay? Buddy. we cannot be here
right now. We gotta go.
What am I going back to?
What?
I don't know if I can prove
I didn't do anything wrong.
Now. I can't force you to come with me.
Okay. I probably could.
but I'm not gonna do that to you.
I'm not.
Now. you can stay here
and you can take your chances
with the Vietnamese consulate.
or whatever you wanna do.
That's your choice.
But I promise you
that if you come with me.
I will do everything in my power
to keep you safe.
to find the truth.
and to give you your life back.
Jay?
Hey. look at me.
I believe you.
And sometimes. the right thing isn't easy.
Let's go.
Last piece is yours.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Saving up for the welcome buffet.
I'm assuming you guys do that. right?
All the time.
This is our ride.
Wait. one sec.
While it's just the two of us.
there's something I haven't told you.
What?
The SARs. I said they involved
several American companies
transferring money to a crypto wallet.
What I didn't tell you is that wallet
is suspected to belong
to a terrorist group.
What?
Three weeks ago.
I sent Wallace a memo trying to warn him
that I believed this group
was a threat to American interests
and we should share this intel
with the FBI.
Shut me down.
Told me I was grasping at straws.
What. you think this terrorist group
is planning something?
No. I think they already pulled it off.
What are you talking about?
I'm pretty sure that wallet
belongs to Raúl Zapata and the LFS.
Jay. are you saying
you predicted the attack on Pima 12?
Not the specifics. but…
And if what I suspect is true.
that would mean that--
Someone stateside funded the attack.
Who?
I don't know.
We'll figure it out together. right?
Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. let's go.
It's not me.
Peter. you okay?
Yeah. you go on ahead.
I'll catch up. I gotta take this.
Hello?
Peter!
I see you kept the phone.
Well. I'm glad you remembered our deal.
A real man of your word.
So. what's it been?
Ten?
Eleven months?
What do you want?
Straight to business. I can respect that.
I'm calling. Peter. because
it appears
that you have something I want.
Or rather…
someone.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org